<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eloquent in investing on</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/</link><description>Recent content in Eloquent in investing on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 18:50:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/about/</guid><description>Hafzan Holdings is an Indian multinational conglomerate holding company headquartered in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. We’re investing for the future on behalf of our clients, inspiring our employees, and supporting our local communities. Our purpose is to help more and more people experience financial well-being. Together with our clients, we’re contributing to a more equitable and resilient world – today and for generations to come. At Hafzan Holdings, we believe we’re at our best when our employees connect their personal purpose to their work and our firm’s purpose.</description></item><item><title>Global Markets</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/global-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 18:50:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/global-markets/</guid><description>Our Global Markets business powers performance via a full range of liquidity, risk management and financing solutions as well as ideas and content tailored to your needs, coupled with execution capabilities across the spectrum of financial products. 1. Macro Fixed Income Financing provides the stability and liquidity you require through the financing of rates, credit and securitised products. Access our services to optimize your funding profile and leverage our specialists to source and facilitate trades with liquidity providers in repo markets.</description></item><item><title>Investment Banking</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/investment-banking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 18:50:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/investment-banking/</guid><description>Advisory, finance and risk management services that connect your ideas to capital and power possibilities. 1. Mergers &amp; Acquisitions Our M&amp;A group can help you tackle your most complex transactions. Together with industry and country coverage colleagues, this global team provides expert advice for all M&amp;A services and strategies, including defense/activism options, shareholder engagement, divestitures, ESG, fairness opinions, joint ventures, leveraged buyouts, restructuring, special committee assignments, valuations and transaction structures 2.</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/research/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 18:50:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/research/</guid><description>Amid market volatility, sector disruption and macroeconomic shifts, our Research team generates powerful, data-led insights to help institutional investors make informed decisions that deliver results. 1. Equity Research With senior analysts covering hundreds of stocks across the Americas and Europe, our Equity Research teams deliver event analysis, stock ideas and sector themes. By collaborating with Credit Research counterparts and Strategists, as well as Thematic, ESG and Data Science teams, they offer clients unique, cross-asset perspectives that challenge conventional wisdom about an industry or market.</description></item><item><title>Solutions</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 18:50:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/solutions/</guid><description>Advisory, finance and risk management services that connect your ideas to capital and power possibilities. 1. Investment Banking Providing large corporate, government and institutional clients with a full spectrum of strategic advisory, financing and risk management solutions. Read More →
2. Global Markets We serve our institutional investor clients by helping them to understand developments in global markets and offering execution and risk management tools across each major asset class. Read More →</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 14:29:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/newsletter/</guid><description>Follow our mission to make the easiest and most fun Hugo starter for building modern websites.</description></item><item><title>Showcase</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/showcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:04:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/showcase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Themes</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/themes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:04:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/themes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:25:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/contact/</guid><description>hello at gethyas.com</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for We run Plausible analytics on gethyas.</description></item></channel></rss>