<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring the Future of Global Trade</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/exploring-the-future-of-global-trade/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/exploring-the-future-of-global-trade/</guid><description>Global trade has long been a driving force behind the global economy, allowing countries to specialize in the production of certain goods and services and exchange them with other countries. In recent years, however, the future of global trade has been called into question due to a variety of factors, including the rise of protectionist policies, the increasing use of technology to automate production, and the impact of climate change.</description></item><item><title>The Economic Impact of the Pandemic: A Retrospective</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/the-economic-impact-of-the-pandemic-a-retrospective/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/the-economic-impact-of-the-pandemic-a-retrospective/</guid><description>The economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic has been unprecedented and far-reaching, with businesses shutting down and people losing their jobs or experiencing reduced income. In this blog post, we will take a retrospective look at the economic effects of the pandemic and consider how it has impacted different industries and regions around the world.
One of the most immediate and noticeable impacts of the pandemic was the shuttering of non-essential businesses, such as retail stores and restaurants, in an effort to slow the spread of the virus.</description></item><item><title>The Economics of Renewable Energy</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/the-economics-of-renewable-energy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/the-economics-of-renewable-energy/</guid><description>The economics of renewable energy is a topic of increasing importance as the world seeks to transition to cleaner, more sustainable sources of energy. Renewable energy sources, such as solar, wind, and hydroelectric, have the potential to reduce our reliance on fossil fuels and mitigate the negative environmental impacts of energy production.
One key advantage of renewable energy is that it can provide a more stable and predictable source of energy compared to fossil fuels, which are subject to price fluctuations due to factors such as supply disruptions and geopolitical tensions.</description></item><item><title>Debt and Economic Growth: A Fine Balance</title><link>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/debt-and-economic-growth-a-fine-balance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ammanullah.github.io/hafzan/blog/debt-and-economic-growth-a-fine-balance/</guid><description>Debt and economic growth are two concepts that are often discussed in relation to each other, but the relationship between them is complex and multifaceted. Economic growth refers to the increase in a country&amp;rsquo;s production of goods and services over a period of time, while debt refers to the borrowing of money by individuals, businesses, or governments.
On the one hand, some economists argue that debt can be a useful tool for promoting economic growth.</description></item></channel></rss>